excuse me
are you two a couple?
Oh my God! I… I love your Instagram.
you mind telling us
how long you've been together?
Oh. It's three months strong.
Like. has it been three months?
No. it's been on and off
for a year and a half.
but. like.
with. like. emotional time zones.
it's really giving.
like. three years. you know?
Yes. but officially it's three months.
We met really fast.
but now we're taking it really slow. and--
-Yeah.
-I like it.
We're doing it the right way.
We are. 'cause. you know.
it's… it's all a process.
So about that. Are… are you ready
to start the process now?
I know you're here to freeze your eggs.
I know you wanna have a child.
And it's my job to give you
the best odds of that happening.
And right now. that means makin' embryos.
not freezin' eggs.
Embryos? Embryos?
Embryo--
♪ Okay
One time for the big girls in the crowd ♪
♪ Hey! Hear me now ♪
♪ Go on. sis. yeah
Show 'em how to work it out ♪
I wanna have a kid.
and if that means I have to start now.
then I start now.
Okay. so you'll use a donor?
A donor?
What? Ew. like a donor kebab?
Sorry. I'm hungry.
Because that means I would. like. need.
like. um… like. a baby daddy.
or. like. a sperm person.
a person with sperm to give me.
Yeah. and I'm assuming
that's your partner?
Oh my God. no. No.
-That's hila… No.
-No.
I'm not the partner. I'm the partnah.
No hard R. With the "ah."
I'm just the best friend. I'm not here
for the embryos. I'm here for support.
He's like a well-made bra.
just uplifting and supportive.
-Yeah.
-Okay. well. who… who's Marley Williams?
-Oh. she's no longer with us.
-Yeah.
My… my condolences.
-Oh. no. she not dead.
-No!
-She alive. She alive. She's in Portugal.
-Yeah. You know what. doc?
A broken heart will make you book
a one-way ticket to Portugal
on a sabbatical from America.
-Yeah.
-Okay. and who's Luca Berrada?
My boyfriend.
He's just so sweet and so kind.
Like. how did that happen?
I would tell you how we met.
but you don't wanna know.
Okay.
Boy. I wish I had time to enjoy this.
Look. you have until your
next menstrual cycle begins to decide.
Freezin' eggs. not the move.
With PCOS and geriatric age…
Okay. that's a little rude. Geriatric age?
But. you know.
it sounds like your Luca guy.
that he… he'd be a good choice.
Are you saying I should ask my boyfriend
to be my baby's father?
I can't believe
it's all happening so fast. I'm nervous.
God. I mean.
Luca and I just got good good.
I can't bring something
this big up right now.
I mean. he just saw me in my bonnet.
Look. you got this. All right.
I mean. look. you gotta talk to Luca.
What does he know?
Um. well. he knows that I'm interested
in freezing eggs for the future.
But now. just after 2.240 hours.
I'm gonna ask Luca to combine DNA with me
forever and all of time?
It's just too much. It's too fast.
-That's too much too fast.
-Hey. Mavis. Mavis.
Hey. take a beat. all right?
Remember to be kind to yourself.
-That was beautiful.
-Yeah.
-You get that from a fortune cookie?
-Surprisingly. no.
I got it from a pamphlet
at my new doctor's office.
Oh.
You know they charge $30
just to sit in a seat?
-Yeah. it's called a co-pay.
-They wanna know your family history.
How the fuck am I supposed to know
if my dad got diabetes?
Oh. that's so easy
because every dad has diabetes.
-Yeah. but every nigga ain't got a dad.
-Wow!
Okay. Questlove.
I didn't know you were writing poetry.
-Hmm.
-You're right.
The only thing I know about my pops is
that he's in prison.
so I'm just gonna guess.
-Right? I mean. that's what doctors do.
-No. they don't. Khalil.
Maybe the ones that charge sliding scale
and ask to see your tongue
before you walk in or whatever.
-It's called homeopathic.
-You don't even know how to spell that.
I thought it was funny.
Honey. this is it!
Girl.
Oh my God. This dress is a moment!
Thank you. Greta. I know you betta.
Ayo. I get to go
to the fashion Illuminati dinner!
It's exciting.
Oh my God. It is so exclusive.
I heard they have those memory erasers
from Men in Black.
so you go
and don't even remember you went.
Oh. that's news to me.
What else you got?
I heard you either have to be royalty
or related to Beyoncé.
Oh my God. we have arrived!
First the FID. then the Met.
and who knows?
Maybe BET. That's a three-letter party.
The Met is so yesterday.
More like Anna "Last" Wintour.
FID is who's up next.
and as for the BET Awards…
Greta. no. You're not allowed
to comment on the BET Awards anymore.
-You know that.
-Right.
And you. you're welcome for the invite.
I have said thank you so many times.
You know what Khalil sent me?
He sent me a beautiful painting
and a fine single malt Scotch.
Oh wow. Okay.
Thank you so much again. Charles Renee.
for inviting me and Khalil to the FID
for a collaboration we did for you
to put money in your pocket
and build your brand.
Stop.
You don't have to actually say thank you.
Kinda makes you sound desperate.
Oh. I sound desperate? I'm the one
that sounds desperate. That is rich.
Hey. tell me about this suit.
Oh. okay.
Well. um. this is just something
I'm working on.
um. for my own line one day.
Because I've always been interested
in doing something gender neutral.
but neutral isn't the word. right?
But. like. gender is a construct.
so I don't know what it is yet.
but I'm definitely gonna find it.
It's gonna be bold and beautiful.
and did you even know
that heels were made for men originally?
-Like. nobody talks about that--
-Hoo. that's a lotta words.
Listen. the collab. it's working.
but let's be honest.
Mavis. you're a long way away
from being a designer.
It's good on you for trying though.
I'll see you at FID tomorrow.
and. hey. don't you act brand-new.
-Greta. can I see you please? Thank you.
-Wait.
But that's confusing
'cause I am brand-new.
Step four. You may…
Oh. oh fuck. Oh shit.
…to make sure…
Okay.
Bubbles.
Okay. One. two. three.
Ah! No.
In and out. In and out.
Like a bank robbery. Let's go. Here we go.
Mmm-ah… Okay.
No. No! No.
I wanna… I wanna…
No.
Khalil! Khalil!
Hey!
Oh-hoo!
Okay. I see you stuntin'.
Thank you so much.
It's giving diva Beetlejuice.
I feel like we fly as fuck right now.
but let's address this big-ass needle.
-What is this?
-Good follow-up.
So. um.
I have to start taking my shots today
because Mother Nature rang.
and I had to pick up the phone.
You know what I'm saying?
So I need help with my shot
'cause I can't do it. Can you help me?
And you knew you had to take this shot.
but you got dressed first.
Hey. Gayle King.
I need more action. less questions.
-Okay. Let's…
-Okay.
-Have you ever held a needle before?
-Yes.
-You have?
-Yeah.
Are you sure? You haven't seen Rent.
You're like. "I can't stand that singing."
I may have not seen Rent.
but I've seen New Jack City.
That's almost a documentary on needles.
Give it here.
Here you go. Okay.
just poke me like you like me. right?
-Okay. I--
-That's weird. Okay.
But put it in like you love me.
Again. a very weird sentence. Here we go.
-You ready?
-Yeah. I'm ready.
-Let's do this.
-Okay.
You know who should really be doing this?
Yes. I do know. Okay?
And I'll talk to him about it tomorrow.
But right now. I gotta do it now. Okay?
'Cause I'm a dot. dot. dot.
forward slash. period.
-Okay.
-Please just help me.
-All right. Give me positive thoughts.
-Okay.
-Okay. Rotisserie chicken at Costco.
-That's good.
Sesame Street. Um…
Nicki Minaj before she was a Republican.
Three!
Why are we screaming?
It's no big deal.
but I had to start my shots today.
and they're all timed.
Okay. Is this for the egg freezing?
Oh-ho. no. brother.
We way past egg freezing.
-Hey. Khalil.
-Yes.
You wanna eat that pizza outside?
No. I'm good.
Oh. 'cause y'all not… You not good. Okay.
Put that back in there.
and then I'll wait on the car outside.
Mm.
-I think I have a car pulling up.
-Yeah. me too.
All right.
So. uh. breaking news.
Have a seat. It's really fun… stuff.
Um… the doctor told me
that I am too old to freeze my eggs.
So basically.
if I wanna have a baby. which I really do.
I have to start making embryos… now.
I thought you wanted to… to wait.
Yeah. I do wanna wait.
I mean. I did wanna wait.
but it's not up to me.
It's up to my body. the universe.
Mother Nature. Father Time.
Take your pick.
It is so fun being a woman.
Okay. hold on. This is a lot.
So you took Khalil to your doctor.
and now you're going to make a baby?
Oh my God.
I'm not having a baby with Khalil. Luca.
He just came with me
to my doctor's appointment
because he's my support system.
Okay. but why didn't you tell me
any of this?
It feels like you're shutting me out.
Do you even want me to be involved?
Do you wanna be involved?
Do you want me to want to be involved?
Okay. Um. I don't have time
for this conversation right now.
All right? I gotta go.
and we can talk about this later.
After you. milady.
Absolutely not. kind sir.
After you.
No. I can't. I shan't.
I mustn't. After you.
On this day. do not insult me. I must say…
After you.
Can you two Black Judi Denches
wrap this up?
I need to see some ID.
Of course you do. good sir.
Yes. guv'nor.
-That's fine.
-Not into it. I'll be quick.
-It's fine.
-One second. Is that…
-I gotta get rid of the water.
-It's in there.
Do you want some water? You look thirsty.
Wait. no. not thirsty like that.
It's… Oh. here it is.
All right.
Look at that.
-Cute pic. right?
-Mavis Beaumont.
That's me.
-Step right this way.
-Okay. great.
After you!
Introducing Mavis Beaumont
of ReMavessance.
-You look the fuck good!
-♪ A bitch look good… ♪
-Get out there. girl.
-♪ A bitch look haute ♪
-♪ A bitch look pretty… ♪
-Oh. hey. everyone.
-♪ A bitch look haute… ♪
-Wassup?
Oh my God. get my good side!
-It's all my sides.
-♪ I'm feelin' so sexy… ♪
-Whoa!
-Mavis. right here.
Put it in portrait mode. girl.
♪ This is that wake up
And look in the mirror like yes ♪
♪ I'm feeling sexy. if I keep on… ♪
Okay.
-Introducing Khalil Holland…
-I can't believe I didn't fall!
-Ask me who styled me.
-Who styled you?
Mavis Beaumont. my best friend.
That's me. That's me.
You look good. boy. Boy. you look good!
Ah!
You look like a pimp that's good at math.
-Fractions only.
-♪ A bitch look good ♪
Oh my God. Khalil. look at us!
This is the Oscars of fashion.
This is the Emmys of art.
This is the Olympics of wedgies.
This is… this is the type of event
that they don't even let
regular people google. okay?
Everybody dressed like
they only drink name-brand soda.
-Nobody know what a Dr. Popper is.
-No. they fucking don't!
Oh. Khalil. we belong here.
Mavis Beaumont.
Hi.
You weren't lying.
You were… actually invited.
Yeah. I was.
Natasha. it's so good to see you.
It is. isn't it?
It is. Yeah. Where's Bruce?
Mavis. Oh my God. Hi!
-Hi.
-What are you doing down there?
-They're strict about bringing a guest.
So I always sneak him in.
I can't go anywhere without him.
Well. they were gonna let me in.
but we were already in the outfit. so…
Yeah.
I love this for you guys.
It's completely normal.
Uh. Khalil. you've met Bruce.
but this is Natasha.
Yeah. what's up. Bruce?
Uh. yeah. of course. Natasha.
I. uh. had the biggest crush on you
in high school. and I used to…
you know. uh. deeply admire
your Sports Illustrated covers.
This is a good story. I'll be right back.
-Jergens or Aveeno?
-Jergens.
Oh. a tree.
Oh. hello. Felita Harris.
founder of RAISEfashion.
No big deal. Just casually talking
to Charlie from Harbison Studios.
Four Met Gala looks.
Like. who's counting? Me! Wow!
I'm just gonna go find the bathroom.
Oh… my God!
Zerina Akers.
I love you so much. Oh my God.
You styled Keke and Beyoncé.
and other notable Black women
with very famous first names.
and no big deal.
Am I still talking? Ashley Graham?!
Did you know it's you?
Yeah. girl. I knew.
This look is iconic.
Oh my God.
Thank you so much. my thick lady.
Girl. you are so weird. I love it!
You wanna join us?
I have to do something right now. but BRB.
You just got here.
And I'll be right back. I promise.
and I miss you so much. and Santa's real.
Oh my God. No.
No!
Oh my God.
How do I have two shades of lipstick.
a pizza crust. but no shot?
Khalil.
-Khalil. Hi.
-Yeah. yes. What's up?
-Where… Yo. where have you been?
-Where have you been?
Yo. I just heard a whole titty popped out.
You ain't never seen Julia Fox DJ?
Catch up. I got bigger problems.
-Bigger than titties?
-Yes.
I got a double-D dilemma. okay?
I need to take another shot.
and I forgot it at home.
A'ight. hit Luca.
He'll bring it over here.
I don't know
if I can call Luca right now to do that.
Oh. okay. A'ight.
Rapid-fire style right now.
Fashion party of your dreams
or make a baby?
Come on now. Why do I have to choose?
You wanna make your inner child proud
or let your doubt win?
Inner child.
Do you trust anyone more than me
to help you with this?
Mave. go call your man.
Eight sessions of therapy.
and all of a sudden you're fucking Karamo?
God.
-Money well spent.
-Know-it-all.
Love you. Anybody else need some advice?
Okay. give me a minute. Okay. Let's see.
Oh. Mavis. I can't find it.
It's behind the rosé.
No. not the can. the bottle.
Not that bottle. The big bottle.
The other big bottle.
Do you know there's wine
that is not pink? I can get you some.
Okay. my booze. my business. boo-boo.
Let's go.
Oh. Trovato. Grande. I'm leaving now.
You're my hero.
Okay. I'm coming. Bye.
Bruce. you finally made it
from up under there. huh?
Oh. yeah. Well. I'm out on good behavior.
Champagne?
-No.
-Of course.
-I brought my own.
-Oh.
I don't know where that came from.
and they're not getting my fingerprints.
So you don't trust the people around here?
No. I mean. I don't trust anybody.
Doesn't matter who.
People.
-Businesses.
-Thank you.
Air.
The post office?
Alexa.
Siri.
All them bitches.
QR codes.
Hand… sanitizer.
♪ She's sexy! ♪
♪ Mister. look at your girl… ♪
-Get out.
-♪ She loves it ♪
♪ Look at her… ♪
-Just so we're clear.
-Yeah.
-This isn't serious.
-Okay.
This poster is a limited edition.
No reprints. no cutouts.
Yeah. I just got out of something serious.
Not even looking for serious.
-Don't look at me.
-Okay.
-Look at me.
-Yeah.
-Take off your clothes.
-Okay.
-Take off your clothes!
-They comin' off.
-All right. let's go.
-Yeah.
♪ Spaceship I want to ride… ♪
♪ She's sexy! ♪
That lasted longer than I thought.
You fuck like you have daddy issues.
And I like that.
Okay.
Cool. man.
Oh. thank you. Reading my mind.
Thank you very much. If I could get
maybe one more in 15. 20 minutes.
Mavis! Mavis!
I want you guys to meet my protégée.
-This is Mavis Beaumont. Please join us.
-Oh my goodness. Nice to meet you guys.
Oh my good… Let me just… Is it behind me?
-It is!
-Yeah. it's right here. Sit.
Oh. you guys look so expensive
and rich and moisturized.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I would introduce myself.
but you know who I am.
I do. LaQuan Smith. How are you?
Your skin looks like Nutella.
I wanna put it on a piece of bread
and eat it.
I see you. too. Jenna motherfuckin' Lyons.
Well. Charles and I were talking
about the fact
that you guys really weathered
some intense press last summer.
Oh. bad press?
What kind of negative press
were we weathering. Charles?
Well. you know. the fashion industry.
as we know. is stuck in the dark ages.
and I know that there's a lot of talk
about how it hasn't changed.
and there's a reason
that plus-size is still niche.
You know. bodies don't stop at a size 12.
but the fashion fantasy does.
I think it's such a shame that
a lot of fatty baddies and oddie bodies
don't get invited to really fancy events
like this one. you know?
And when we are invited.
we can never find anything to wear
because all the industry wants
to make for us is cheetah sweatpants
and cupcake dresses.
I am cupcaked out.
It's insane. You know
what I'm talking about. Jenna Lyons.
I so know.
I really would love plus-size bodies
to have access to beautiful.
architectural. avant-garde realness.
We all want it. We do.
I mean. this is the FID.
It's where art meets fashion.
And I know a lot of people past size 12
who wanna spend their money.
That's my fantasy.
One hundred fucking percent yes.
Thank you.
You know what? Charles.
I think you should keep her around.
Jenna. I'm not even gonna lie.
I think that she is the equation.
She's the solution.
And I'd give her a bit
of extra credit too.
-She ate that.
-Yes. she did.
Yes. she did. You know what?
That is exactly why
Mavis will be joining me
for my Paris Men's Fashion Week debut.
What? For real?
-Wow.
-You're taking me to Paris?
You know what? You… you earned this.
And I need you there.
And honestly.
you work as much as you talk.
-She talks a lot.
-I know.
I do talk a lot. I do feel a lot.
I have big feelings. plus-size feel…
A Costco-sized amount of feelings.
It's very… Okay. I have to go now.
-It was so nice meeting you guys.
-Where are you going? You just got here.
Why does every shiny. cute Black man
keep asking me where I'm goin'?
This is really fun!
Sorry. Sorry.
Okay. so please don't forget…
…to flick out the air bubbles.
It's okay. I got this.
Okay.
Great. and if you don't got it.
it's okay too.
I mean. I can't even do it.
I can go back in and have Khalil do it
or even Ashley Graham
'cause we're best friends now.
She knows I'm a weirdo.
Take a deep breath.
I'm done.
-You are?
-Mm-hmm.
How?
I did the research online.
If you pinch before. it doesn't hurt.
Okay. I am. um…
I should've talked to you.
And I'm really sorry
about the Khalil stuff.
I was nervous.
I was nervous because
I know that we. like. dreamt about it
and we talked about it.
But now it's here. It's real. you know?
It's like. do you…
wanna have a child with me?
I mean. there's so many things that
we have to plan that are so unplanned.
Like. where are we gonna live?
How are we gonna afford this?
Like. there's so much to plan.
but you've always known
that I wanted a baby. right?
But are you…
are you even ready to have a child?
Are we even ready to have a chil…
like. a whole child together?
There are so many things
we haven't done as a couple.
I've never even met your mama in person.
just on FaceTime.
And. I… Luca. I have
to make hard decisions right now
because I'm walking
into my forties so fast.
And I just…
-Mavis.
-Yeah.
I didn't move here for you.
I moved here for us.
Okay. why do you always say
the most perfect things?
I know things are out of order
for both of us.
But whatever order it is.
I wanna do it with you.
I wanted kids one day
with the right person.
You are that person.
Luca Mohammed Berrada.
may I have your sperm to fertilize my egg
so we can make a embryo?
Mavis Jolene Beaumont…
…you can have all my sperm.
Even though that sounds weird.
I love us.
Good to see you again.
Glad you're ready to continue.
-We're more than ready.
-Perfect.
So how about you go fill this up?
Oh.
Do I need to be here for this?
-Yes. you do.
-I don't think so.
♪ Betta know about me. babe ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I'm way too lit. I'm way to thick ♪
♪ Talk a lotta trash. but I could bag it ♪
♪ Betta know about me ♪
♪ Mm-mm. yeah ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Mm-mm. yeah ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Mm-mm. yeah ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Betta know about me. babe ♪